School of Medicine Records UA010
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Subject files, 1885 -- 1994; UA010.001; 13.0 Linear Feet
  - TCCHAP, CPHC (Columbia Point health center) instructions, 1967; UA010.001.016.00006 (Box 16)
  - TCCHAP, CPHC (Columbia Point health center) patterns on service, 1967; UA010.001.016.00007 (Box 16)
  - TCCHAP, curriculum advisory committee, 1967; UA010.001.016.00008 (Box 16)
  - TCCHAP, curriculum, 1965; UA010.001.016.00009 (Box 16)
  - TCCHAP, Cruz, 1967; UA010.001.016.00010 (Box 16)
  - TCCHAP, dental aides, 1967; UA010.001.016.00011 (Box 16)
  - TCCHAP, dental care, 1967; UA010.001.016.00012 (Box 16)
  - TCCHAP, dental clinic, 1967; UA010.001.016.00013 (Box 16)
  - TCCHAP, departments heads meeting, 1969; UA010.001.016.00014 (Box 16)
  - TCCHAP, description of community family services department, 1968; UA010.001.016.00015 (Box 16)
  - TCCHAP, David deTurk, 1967; UA010.001.016.00016 (Box 16)
  - TCCHAP, David deTurk, 1968; UA010.001.016.00017 (Box 16)
  - TCCHAP, development council tenant advisory board, 1968; UA010.001.016.00018 (Box 16)
  - TCCHAP, Dibujos, UA010.001.016.00019 (Box 16)
  - TCCHAP, discussion group, 1967; UA010.001.016.00020 (Box 16)
  - TCCHAP, drug utilization, 1967; UA010.001.016.00021 (Box 16)
  - TCCHAP, early childhood aides, 1968; UA010.001.017.00001 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP, Columbia Point, January - March, 1969; UA010.001.017.00002 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP, emerency meeting racial violence, 1967; UA010.001.017.00003 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP, employee health plan, 1968; UA010.001.017.00005 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP, epidemiology, 1962; UA010.001.017.00006 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP, equipment, 1968; UA010.001.017.00007 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP, executive committee, 1968; UA010.001.017.00008 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP, executive committee minutes, 1968; UA010.001.017.00009 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP, eye program, 1970; UA010.001.017.00010 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP, facilities and furnishings, 1967; UA010.001.017.00011 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP, family agent training proposal, UA010.001.017.00012 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP, family care committee, 1969; UA010.001.017.00013 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP, family health care groups, 1967; UA010.001.017.00014 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP, family health workers assignments, 1967; UA010.001.017.00015 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP, family health workers report, 1967; UA010.001.017.00016 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP, familiy health workers role, 1967; UA010.001.017.00017 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP, family health workers training, 1967; UA010.001.017.00018 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP, family life education, 1967; UA010.001.017.00019 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP, family planning, 1968; UA010.001.017.00020 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP FHCG (family health care group), 1966; UA010.001.017.00021 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP, Dr. Ferraro, Richard, 1968; UA010.001.017.00022 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP, FHW, 1967; UA010.001.017.00023 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP, FHW advancement, 1967; UA010.001.017.00024 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP, FHC chronological file, 1966; UA010.001.017.00025 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP, FHW correspondence, 1968; UA010.001.017.00026 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP, FHW post-training, UA010.001.017.00027 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP, FHW II, 1967; UA010.001.017.00028 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP, FHW raw data, 1967; UA010.001.017.00029 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP, first quarter, 1969; UA010.001.017.00030 (Box 17)
  - TCCHAP, flouridation, 1966; UA010.001.018.00001 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, food project elementary school, UA010.001.018.00002 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, food supplement, UA010.001.018.00003 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, forms, UA010.001.018.00004 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, George McCray sw student, 1969; UA010.001.018.00005 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, Gibson, count, 1968; UA010.001.018.00006 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, grievances, 1968; UA010.001.018.00007 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, grievance committee, 1968; UA010.001.018.00008 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, group III, 1969; UA010.001.018.00009 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, group III, 1969; UA010.001.018.00010 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, group dynamics, UA010.001.018.00011 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, group home proposal, 1969; UA010.001.018.00012 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, health association, 1967; UA010.001.018.00013 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, health association, 1968; UA010.001.018.00014 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, health association, 1968; UA010.001.018.00015 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, health association-current, 1967; UA010.001.018.00016 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, health association fund raising, 1965; UA010.001.018.00017 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, health association residents meeting, 1965; UA010.001.018.00018 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, health center information, UA010.001.018.00019 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, health center social service, 1968; UA010.001.018.00020 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, health center staff, UA010.001.018.00021 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, health education, 1967; UA010.001.018.00022 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, health education classification system, 1957; UA010.001.018.00023 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, health education funding, 1956; UA010.001.018.00024 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, HC program committee, 1966; UA010.001.018.00025 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, homemaker program, UA010.001.018.00026 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, hospital lists, UA010.001.018.00027 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, housing problems, 1967; UA010.001.018.00028 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, information kit, 1967; UA010.001.018.00029 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, in-service training, 1968; UA010.001.018.00030 (Box 18)
  - TCCHAP, inter-office memos, 1968; UA010.001.019.00001 (Box 19)
  - TCCHAP, interservice english course, UA010.001.019.00002 (Box 19)
  - TCCHAP, interstaff, 1969; UA010.001.019.00003 (Box 19)
  - TCCHAP, Isenberg, Phillip, 1968; UA010.001.019.00004 (Box 19)
  - TCCHAP, Jean's correspondence, 1966; UA010.001.019.00005 (Box 19)
  - TCCHAP, job descriptions, 1968; UA010.001.019.00006 (Box 19)
  - TCCHAP, job descriptions, 1969; UA010.001.019.00007 (Box 19)
  - TCCHAP, job description (aide and clerical), 1968; UA010.001.019.00008 (Box 19)
  - TCCHAP, John Cambell, correspondence, 1967; UA010.001.019.00009 (Box 19)
  - TCCHAP, John's file, 1966; UA010.001.019.00010 (Box 19)
  - TCCHAP, joint committees, UA010.001.019.00011 (Box 19)
  - TCCHAP, leaky roofs, 1967; UA010.001.019.00012 (Box 19)
  - TCCHAP, Leon-Bennit Alder, 1970; UA010.001.019.00013 (Box 19)
  - TCCHAP, legal, 1970; UA010.001.019.00014 (Box 19)
  - TCCHAP, library, 1967; UA010.001.019.00015 (Box 19)
  - TCCHAP, low income morgage, 1969; UA010.001.019.00016 (Box 19)
  - TCCHAP, Marylou flood correspondence, 1967; UA010.001.019.00017 (Box 19)
  - TCCHAP, MAW, 1967; UA010.001.019.00018 (Box 19)
  - TCCHAP, measles program, UA010.001.019.00019 (Box 19)
  - TCCHAP, medicaid, 1968; UA010.001.019.00020 (Box 19)
  - TCCHAP, medicaid, 1968; UA010.001.019.00021 (Box 19)
  - TCCHAP, medicaid visits, 1968; UA010.001.019.00022 (Box 19)
  - TCCHAP, McCormack school, 1968; UA010.001.019.00023 (Box 19)
  - TCCHAP, medical assistance, 1967; UA010.001.019.00024 (Box 19)
  - TCCHAP, medical students, 1970; UA010.001.019.00025 (Box 19)
  - TCCHAP, medicare alert, 1965; UA010.001.019.00026 (Box 19)
  - TCCHAP, memos-Krom, 1966; UA010.001.020.00001 (Box 20)
  - TCCHAP, mico, 1966; UA010.001.020.00002 (Box 20)
  - TCCHAP, miscellaneous, 1967; UA010.001.020.00003 (Box 20)
  - TCCHAP, monthly reports, 1970; UA010.001.020.00004 (Box 20)
  - TCCHAP, monthly reports, 1970; UA010.001.020.00005 (Box 20)
  - TCCHAP, mothers group, 1967; UA010.001.020.00006 (Box 20)
  - TCCHAP, mound bayou, 1966 -- 1967; UA010.001.020.00007 (Box 20)
  - TCCHAP, mound bayou, 1968 -- 1969; UA010.001.020.00008 (Box 20)
  - TCCHAP, mound bayou, 1970; UA010.001.020.00009 (Box 20)
  - TCCHAP, mound bayou, 1971 -- 1972; UA010.001.020.00010 (Box 20)
  - TCCHAP, mound bayou miscellaneous, UA010.001.020.00011 (Box 20)
  - TCCHAP, mound bayou printed material, 1968; UA010.001.021.00001 (Box 21)
  - TCCHAP, neighborhood action center, 1967; UA010.001.021.00002 (Box 21)
  - TCCHAP, neighborhood action project, 1965; UA010.001.021.00003 (Box 21)
  - TCCHAP, neighborhood health centers, 1967; UA010.001.021.00004 (Box 21)
  - TCCHAP, new HC scheduling, 1968; UA010.001.021.00005 (Box 21)
  - TCCHAP, newsletter, 1968 -- 1969; UA010.001.021.00006 (Box 21)
  - TCCHAP, newspaper clippings, 1965 -- 1967; UA010.001.021.00007 (Box 21)
  - TCCHAP, news clips and press releases, 1968 -- 1970; UA010.001.021.00008 (Box 21)
  - TCCHAP, NYSPA paper, UA010.001.021.00009 (Box 21)
  - TCCHAP, OEO, 1968; UA010.001.021.00010 (Box 21)
  - TCCHAP, OEO meetings, 1965; UA010.001.021.00011 (Box 21)
  - TCCHAP, OEO site visit, 1968; UA010.001.021.00012 (Box 21)
  - TCCHAP, OEO staff meeting, 1965; UA010.001.021.00013 (Box 21)
  - TCCHAP, Oshima, Bill, 1968; UA010.001.022.00001 (Box 22)
  - TCCHAP, Oshima, Cambell-final report, 1967; UA010.001.022.00002 (Box 22)
  - TCCHAP, pavenstedt, 1968; UA010.001.022.00003 (Box 22)
  - TCCHAP, peace corps, 1966; UA010.001.022.00004 (Box 22)
  - TCCHAP, peace corps, 1967; UA010.001.022.00005 (Box 22)
  - TCCHAP, pending, 1967; UA010.001.022.00006 (Box 22)
  - TCCHAP, personnel, 1969; UA010.001.022.00007 (Box 22)
  - TCCHAP, personnel commoittee, 1967; UA010.001.022.00008 (Box 22)
  - TCCHAP, personnel recruitment, 1969; UA010.001.022.00009 (Box 22)
  - TCCHAP, personnel training committee, 1968; UA010.001.022.00010 (Box 22)
  - TCCHAP, PHS contract, 1968; UA010.001.022.00011 (Box 22)
  - TCCHAP, podiatry aides, 1967; UA010.001.022.00012 (Box 22)
  - TCCHAP, preventative medicine, 1969; UA010.001.022.00013 (Box 22)
  - TCCHAP, professional education, UA010.001.022.00014 (Box 22)
  - TCCHAP, professional education at health center, UA010.001.022.00015 (Box 22)
  - TCCHAP, professional staff meeting, 1967; UA010.001.022.00016 (Box 22)
  - TCCHAP, program planning evaluation, 1961; UA010.001.022.00017 (Box 22)
  - TCCHAP, progress report CPDC, 1965 -- 1966; UA010.001.022.00018 (Box 22)
  - TCCHAP, projects, 1967; UA010.001.022.00019 (Box 22)
  - TCCHAP, program for selection/training, 1967; UA010.001.022.00020 (Box 22)
  - TCCHAP, psychiatry, 1970; UA010.001.022.00021 (Box 22)
  - TCCHAP, Puerto Ricans, 1968; UA010.001.022.00022 (Box 22)
  - TCCHAP, Puerto Rican family diagnosis, 1967; UA010.001.022.00023 (Box 22)
  - TCCHAP, public housing, 1967; UA010.001.022.00024 (Box 22)
  - TCCHAP, public schools, UA010.001.022.00025 (Box 22)
  - TCCHAP, public welfare, 1970; UA010.001.022.00026 (Box 22)
  - TCCHAP, quarterly reports, 1968; UA010.001.023.00001 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP, quarterly reports, 1969; UA010.001.023.00002 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP, rats and roaches, 1967; UA010.001.023.00003 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP, raw data on extermination, UA010.001.023.00004 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP, referrals, 1967; UA010.001.023.00005 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP, references, 1968; UA010.001.023.00006 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP, reorganization, 1968; UA010.001.023.00007 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP, research department, 1970; UA010.001.023.00008 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP, research evaluation, 1964; UA010.001.023.00009 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP, resources, 1966; UA010.001.023.00010 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP, review, 1968; UA010.001.023.00011 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP, Riessman: training (non-professional), 1964 -- 1965; UA010.001.023.00012 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP, Robert Manke, 1967; UA010.001.023.00013 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP, Rudy Sellers, 1967; UA010.001.023.00014 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP, Rudy Sellers memos, 1967; UA010.001.023.00015 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP, Rudy and John, 1967; UA010.001.023.00016 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP, salaries, 1969; UA010.001.023.00017 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP, selection: non-professional, UA010.001.023.00018 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP. senior citizens, 1969; UA010.001.023.00019 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP, sex education, UA010.001.023.00020 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP, signed communications contract, 1967; UA010.001.023.00021 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP, social service coordination group, 1969; UA010.001.023.00022 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP, social service report, UA010.001.023.00023 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP, spanish speaking, 1967; UA010.001.023.00024 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP, social service technician, 1969; UA010.001.023.00025 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP, special projects, 1967; UA010.001.023.00026 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP, social services department, 1968; UA010.001.023.00027 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP, social services department, 1969 -- 1971; UA010.001.023.00028 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP, social services department staff meetings, 1969; UA010.001.023.00029 (Box 23)
  - TCCHAP, social service evaluation, 1970; UA010.001.024.00001 (Box 24)
  - TCCHAP, social service exchange, 1966 -- 1967; UA010.001.024.00002 (Box 24)
  - TCCHAP, SSW monthly reports, 1970; UA010.001.024.00003 (Box 24)
  - TCCHAP, social work assistant, UA010.001.024.00004 (Box 24)
  - TCCHAP, social work staff, 1970; UA010.001.024.00005 (Box 24)
  - TCCHAP, social worker conference, 1967; UA010.001.024.00006 (Box 24)
  - TCCHAP, staff conference, 1970; UA010.001.024.00007 (Box 24)
  - TCCHAP, staff newsletter, 1970; UA010.001.024.00008 (Box 24)
  - TCCHAP, staff orientation evaluation, 1969; UA010.001.024.00009 (Box 24)
  - TCCHAP, summerthing, 1969; UA010.001.024.00010 (Box 24)
  - TCCHAP, survey on migrant labor, 1963; UA010.001.024.00011 (Box 24)
  - TCCHAP, TAB, 1968; UA010.001.024.00012 (Box 24)
  - TCCHAP, task force, 1967; UA010.001.024.00013 (Box 24)
  - TCCHAP, task force (non professionals), 1968; UA010.001.024.00014 (Box 24)
  - TCCHAP, teaching aide references, UA010.001.024.00015 (Box 24)
  - TCCHAP, teamwork training, 1966; UA010.001.024.00016 (Box 24)
  - TCCHAP, teenage survey, 1966; UA010.001.024.00017 (Box 24)
  - TCCHAP, teenage survey, 1966; UA010.001.024.00018 (Box 24)
  - TCCHAP, teenage survey, 1966; UA010.001.025.00001 (Box 25)
  - TCCHAP, teenage survey, 1966; UA010.001.025.00002 (Box 25)
  - TCCHAP, teenage survey, 1969; UA010.001.025.00003 (Box 25)
  - TCCHAP, teenage survey, 1966; UA010.001.025.00004 (Box 25)
  - TCCHAP, teenage survey, 1966; UA010.001.025.00005 (Box 25)
  - TCCHAP, tot lot project, 1967; UA010.001.025.00006 (Box 25)
  - TCCHAP, trainees, 1967; UA010.001.025.00007 (Box 25)
  - TCCHAP, training, 1970; UA010.001.025.00008 (Box 25)
  - TCCHAP, training FHW, 1968; UA010.001.025.00009 (Box 25)
  - TCCHAP, training project, UA010.001.026.00001 (Box 26)
  - TCCHAP, training task force, 1968; UA010.001.026.00002 (Box 26)
  - TCCHAP, Tufts mental health program, 1968; UA010.001.026.00003 (Box 26)
  - TCCHAP, unclassified statistics, 1969; UA010.001.026.00004 (Box 26)
  - TCCHAP, upward bound, UA010.001.026.00005 (Box 26)
  - TCCHAP, voting league, 1967; UA010.001.026.00006 (Box 26)
  - TCCHAP, weekly reports, 1967; UA010.001.026.00007 (Box 26)
  - TCCHAP, welfare department, 1967; UA010.001.026.00008 (Box 26)
  - TCCHAP, weekly reports, 1966; UA010.001.026.00009 (Box 26)
  - TCCHAP, weight control group, 1967; UA010.001.026.00010 (Box 26)
  - TCCHAP, welfare department, 1967; UA010.001.026.00011 (Box 26)
  - TCCHAP, welfare pamphlet, 1967; UA010.001.026.00012 (Box 26)
  - TCCHAP, welfare rights manual, UA010.001.026.00013 (Box 26)
  - TCCHAP, workshop, 1966; UA010.001.026.00014 (Box 26)
  - TCCHAP, Yankelovich report, 1966; UA010.001.026.00015 (Box 26)
  - TCCHAP, "750" proposal, 1969; UA010.001.026.00016 (Box 26)
  - William Harvey Society, 1937 -- 1938; UA010.001.026.00017 (Box 26)
  - Worcester Foundation of Experimantal Biology, 1945; UA010.001.026.00018 (Box 26)
- Office of the Dean, Subject files, 1882 -- 1989; UA010.002; 13.2 Linear Feet
  These files were accessioned prior to the reopening of the archives in 1997. The majority of the material seems to originate from the office of the dean of the medical school, and were grouped into subject files in alphabetical order. In processing this series, items that were out of order were put back into their proper place in the alphabetical range.
  This series contains files from the AAUP, the ad hoc affiliation committee, the admissions department, The Area Health Education Center, general alumni files, alumni weekends and reunions, the medical alumni association, the dept. of anatomy, the animal farm committe, the arborway renal clinic, several folders of files dealing with Dean Banks, BCH, Boston City Hospital, Boston VA's medical center, the board of trustees, the Medical School's budgets, the capitol campaign, the center for birth defects, The council of the deans, school curriculum, the dean's advisory committee, educational development program, educational media department, environmental health program, faculty rosters, fundraising, foundation applications, the Framingham Union Hospital, The HSEB (reports, committees, grants) the Health Sciences Library, the Human Investigations Review Committee, the Kennedy Memorial, the Laboratory Building Committee, the Learning Resources Committee, the Lemuuel Shattuck Hospital, the Maine Medical Center, the Office of the Dean of Medicine, the medical education database, the NEMCH, the Newton Wellesley Hospital, the North Shore Children's Hospital, the Office of Planning and Evaluation, Parent's days, Penobscot Bay Medical Center, the Personel Department, position emmision tomography, the Primary Care Committee, Project Hope, Quincy City Hospital, research protocols, research symposiums, the Sackler Center for Health, St. Elizabeth's Hospital, St. Margaret's Hospital, the Student Promotions Committee, St. Vincent's Hospital, TUSM affiliation data, TNEMC, minutes of the University Council, and the Whitaker Funds papers.
  - AAUP (American Association of University Professors), 1981; UA010.002.027.00001 (Box 27)
  - Academic award preventative cardiology, 1977 -- 1981; UA010.002.027.00002 (Box 27)
  - Ad hoc affiliation comm general correspondence, 1969 -- 1971; UA010.002.027.00003 (Box 27)
  - Ad hoc affiliation comm general correspondence, 1972; UA010.002.027.00004 (Box 27)
  - Ad hoc administration commgeneral correspondence, 1973; UA010.002.027.00005 (Box 27)
  - Ad hoc affiliation comm list of affiliated institutions, 1969 -- 1970; UA010.002.027.00006 (Box 27)
  - Ad hoc comm on curriculum review, 1982; UA010.002.027.00007 (Box 27)
  - Admissions, 1981 -- 1983; UA010.002.027.00008 (Box 27)
  - Admissions, 1983 -- 1984; UA010.002.027.00009 (Box 27)
  - Admissions, 1984 -- 1986; UA010.002.027.00010 (Box 27)
  - Admissions, 1987; UA010.002.027.00011 (Box 27)
  - Admissions interviewers, 1987; UA010.002.027.00012 (Box 27)
  - Admissions policy committee, 1981; UA010.002.027.00013 (Box 27)
  - Advisory task force on financial accounting, 1882; UA010.002.027.00014 (Box 27)
  - Affairs, Committee on Educational, 1970 -- 1986; UA010.002.027.00015 (Box 27)
  - Affairs, Committee on Faculty, 1970 -- 1986; UA010.002.027.00016 (Box 27)
  - Affairs, Committee on Faculty, 1970 -- 1986; UA010.002.027.00017 (Box 27)
  - AHEC (Area Health Education Center) of Pioneer Valley inc, 1972 -- 1980; UA010.002.027.00018 (Box 27)
  - AHEC, 1972 -- 1980; UA010.002.027.00019 (Box 27)
  - AHEC, 1972 -- 1980; UA010.002.027.00020 (Box 27)
  - Aho, Chris, 1988; UA010.002.027.00021 (Box 27)
  - Aisen, Mae W, 1984; UA010.002.027.00022 (Box 27)
  - Alumni bulletin, 1970 -- 1986; UA010.002.027.00023 (Box 27)
  - Alumni weekend, 1981; UA010.002.027.00024 (Box 27)
  - Alumni weekend, 1980; UA010.002.027.00025 (Box 27)
  - Alumni weekend, 1984; UA010.002.027.00026 (Box 27)
  - Alumni reunion, 1982; UA010.002.027.00027 (Box 27)
  - Alumni reunion, 1983; UA010.002.027.00028 (Box 27)
  - Alumni (medical) association council, 1973; UA010.002.027.00029 (Box 27)
  - Alumni (medical) weekend, 1972; UA010.002.027.00030 (Box 27)
  - Alumni (medical) weekend, 1973; UA010.002.027.00031 (Box 27)
  - Alumni (medical) weekend, 1974; UA010.002.027.00032 (Box 27)
  - Alumni (medical) weekend, 1975; UA010.002.027.00033 (Box 27)
  - Alumni (medical) weekend, 1976; UA010.002.027.00034 (Box 27)
  - Alumni (medical) weekend, 1977; UA010.002.027.00035 (Box 27)
  - Alumni (medical) weekend, 1978; UA010.002.027.00036 (Box 27)
  - Alumni (medical) weekend, 1979; UA010.002.027.00037 (Box 27)
  - Anatomy dept review, 1982; UA010.002.027.00038 (Box 27)
  - Anatomy dept review, 1983; UA010.002.027.00039 (Box 27)
  - Animal care advisory committee, 1977; UA010.002.027.00040 (Box 27)
  - Animal farm committee, 1975; UA010.002.027.00041 (Box 27)
  - Animal farm committee, 1975 -- 1979; UA010.002.027.00042 (Box 27)
  - Arborway Renal Clinic, 1979; UA010.002.027.00043 (Box 27)
  - Archdiocese health care system, 1974; UA010.002.027.00044 (Box 27)
  - Arts and sciences school, 1985; UA010.002.027.00045 (Box 27)
  - Ashford, Nicholas, 1983; UA010.002.028.00001 (Box 28)
  - Assistant dean to students and curriculum affairs, 1983; UA010.002.028.00002 (Box 28)
  - Assistant to vice president for health studies, 1981; UA010.002.028.00003 (Box 28)
  - Associate dean for administration, 1982; UA010.002.028.00004 (Box 28)
  - Associate dean for administration search, 1984; UA010.002.028.00005 (Box 28)
  - Banks (dean) consultation int. health res. and oppos., 1983; UA010.002.028.00006 (Box 28)
  - Banks (dean) consultation int. health res. and oppos., 1983; UA010.002.028.00007 (Box 28)
  - Banks (dean) consultation int. health res. and oppos., 1983; UA010.002.028.00008 (Box 28)
  - Banks (dean) consultation int. health res. and oppos., 1983; UA010.002.028.00009 (Box 28)
  - Basic sciences budget committee, 1983; UA010.002.028.00010 (Box 28)
  - Batter, Lisa, 1982; UA010.002.028.00011 (Box 28)
  - Baystate, 1970 -- 1979; UA010.002.028.00012 (Box 28)
  - Baystate, 1970 -- 1979; UA010.002.028.00013 (Box 28)
  - Baystsate medical center, hospital database, 1970 -- 1979; UA010.002.028.00014 (Box 28)
  - BCH data, 1968 -- 1970; UA010.002.028.00015 (Box 28)
  - BCH orthopedics, 1969; UA010.002.028.00016 (Box 28)
  - Berninger, Ronald W., 1983; UA010.002.028.00017 (Box 28)
  - Blumstein, Michael, 1982; UA010.002.028.00018 (Box 28)
  - Charlton fund committee, 1971; UA010.002.028.00019 (Box 28)
  - Boston City hospital, 1973; UA010.002.028.00020 (Box 28)
  - Boston City Hospital, 1973; UA010.002.028.00021 (Box 28)
  - Boston City Hospital, 1983; UA010.002.028.00022 (Box 28)
  - Boston City Hospital, 1973; UA010.002.028.00023 (Box 28)
  - Boston City Hospital, 1969; UA010.002.028.00024 (Box 28)
  - Boston City Hospital, 1973; UA010.002.028.00025 (Box 28)
  - Boston City Hospital data, UA010.002.028.00026 (Box 28)
  - Boston City Hospital, 1973; UA010.002.028.00027 (Box 28)
  - Boston VA medical center, 1975 -- 1977; UA010.002.028.00028 (Box 28)
  - Boston veterans administration medical center, 1983; UA010.002.028.00029 (Box 28)
  - Board of trustees minutes, 1974 -- 1979; UA010.002.029.00001 (Box 29)
  - Boston VA medical center, 1970 -- 1972; UA010.002.029.00002 (Box 29)
  - Boston VA medical center, 1973; UA010.002.029.00003 (Box 29)
  - Budgets, 1979 -- 1980; UA010.002.029.00004 (Box 29)
  - Budgets, 1980 -- 1981; UA010.002.029.00005 (Box 29)
  - Budgets, 1981 -- 1982; UA010.002.029.00006 (Box 29)
  - Budgets, 1979 -- 1985; UA010.002.029.00007 (Box 29)
  - BSOT space, 1982; UA010.002.029.00008 (Box 29)
  - BSOT space, 1982; UA010.002.029.00009 (Box 29)
  - Capital campaign, 1977 -- 1982; UA010.002.029.00010 (Box 29)
  - Capital campaign, 1977 -- 1982; UA010.002.029.00011 (Box 29)
  - Carakostas, Kichael C, 1983; UA010.002.029.00012 (Box 29)
  - Center for birth defects, 1978 -- 1980; UA010.002.029.00013 (Box 29)
  - Center for birth defects, 1978 -- 1980; UA010.002.029.00014 (Box 29)
  - Center for birth defects, 1982 -- 1983; UA010.002.029.00015 (Box 29)
  - Chelsea soldiers home, 1982; UA010.002.029.00016 (Box 29)
  - Childrens hospital, 1981; UA010.002.029.00017 (Box 29)
  - Challberg, Mark D, 1980; UA010.002.029.00018 (Box 29)
  - City (Boston) Hospital, 1969; UA010.002.029.00019 (Box 29)
  - Committee on teaching nutrition, 1983; UA010.002.029.00020 (Box 29)
  - Council of deans, 1979 -- 1981; UA010.002.029.00021 (Box 29)
  - Council of deans, 1979 -- 1981; UA010.002.029.00022 (Box 29)
  - Council of deans, 1979 -- 1981; UA010.002.029.00023 (Box 29)
  - Council of the dean, 1980 -- 1985; UA010.002.029.00024 (Box 29)